horlicks.in 2018-08-30

# Privacy statement | GSK Consumer Healthcare INDIA

GlaxoSmithKline Consumer Healthcare ("GSKCH") is a global organization, strongly committed to your right to privacy. This Privacy Statement sets forth the policy pertaining to this site [www.gsk-ch.in](http://www.gsk-ch.in/). You agree to comply with all local rules regarding online conduct and acceptable content. Specifically, you agree to comply with all applicable laws regarding the transmission of technical data.

This site may collect the following information:

1\. Personally identifiable information which is used to log a visitor on to the site and make the site customized as per the needs of the visitor. 

2\. Non-personal identifiable information is collected which is used for aggregating purposes and is not disclosed to third parties during such process.

3\. Some voluntary information also gets accumulated which the various visitors type in during the log on process. The visitor voluntarily gives this information and GSKCH does not take any responsibility as regards such information.

GSKCH will only collect personally identifiable data when it is voluntarily submitted to us at this web-site. Information attained by the site is used for the specific purpose for which it was volunteered and is not sold, rented or otherwise distributed to third parties. If there is an instance where such information may be shared, the visitor will be asked for permission beforehand.

However, GSKCH reserves the right to share any such information which at the time of logging on to the web site ([www.gsk-ch.in](http://www.gsk-ch.in/ "www.gsk-ch.in")) a visitor has to fill in for the purpose of availing the services offered by this site, with its affiliates, for the purposes stated above.

GSKCH receives very little personally identifying information from visitors to our Website and only for a narrow set of purposes. Such information is collected and may be used to improve our service, to make our site more user friendly, to conduct market surveys, for growing interest, to get a feed back regarding products of our Company and for such other purposes.

This information collected may consist of basic contact information such as your name, title, company address, e-mail address, and telephone and fax numbers. Other demographic information, such as gender and occupation, is not actively sought. It is GSKCH's policy to limit the information collected to only the minimum information required to fulfill a visitor's request. When personally identifiable information is retained, GSKCH assumes responsibility for keeping an accurate record of the information once a visitor has submitted and verified the data. GSKCH does not assume the responsibility for verifying the on-going accuracy of the content of personal information.

Third party advertising networks that serve advertisements onto any GSKCH web site may use cookies and/or web beacons in their advertisements. GSKCH retains no control over such third party cookies and/or web beacons and does not have access to the information related to third party cookies and/or web beacons. Cookies/Session Objects may be used on some areas of our site. Cookies/Session Objects help us in many ways to make your visit to our website more enjoyable and meaningful to you.

GSKCH makes every practical effort to avoid excessive or irrelevant collection of data. GSKCH will not use data collected from our websites to facilitate unsolicited marketing activities. The web site also uses information in the aggregate form to track the total number of visitors to our site, the number of visitors to each page of our site, and the domain names of our visitors' internet service providers. Web beacons are site instrumentation that help us to determine, for instance, whether a page has been viewed or not and, if so, how many times. No personally identifiable information is disclosed in this process to any third party.

Some of the information we receive is not kept - for example, we usually do not keep mailing addresses for white papers. Contact information about visitors (such as information generated though registration for access to areas on the site) will be kept as long as the information is required to completely service the contact request or until a user requests that we delete that information. Mailing list information, discussion posts and e-mail, if collected, are kept for only the period of time considered reasonable to facilitate the visitor's requests.

As a convenience to our visitors, GSKCH sites contain links to a number of sites that we believe may offer useful information. The Privacy Policy and procedure described here do not apply to those sites. GSKCH assumes no responsibility for the information practices of sites a user is able to access through ours, and encourages visitors to review each site's privacy policy before disclosing any personally identifiable information.

GSKCH understands the importance of protecting children's privacy especially in an online environment. This site has not been intentionally designed for or directed at children under the age of 18 years. GSKCH does not intend to collect personal information from children under the age of 18 years.

GSKCH reserves the right, at its discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this Privacy Policy without prior notice, and such changes shall be communicated to the visitors on this site. Visitors should check this page periodically for changes. Continued use of this site following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy will mean that you accept those changes.

This site is intended for audiences in India only.
